[Music]
welcome to the business Central launch
event thank you for joining us today my
name is Lilman I'm joined by my
colleague Maya
rum today we will look at what's new in
the business Central uh release 2024
Wave
2 we are today broadcasting from the
Microsoft Development Center in Denmark
this is also the home for the global
business Central uh product and
engineering team and today we are joined
by Yanik Bower and Dimitri JV they will
take us through all the details and the
highlights of the release but first
let's look about a little into what you
can expect from micros oft with this
release Maya you have been busy last
couple of weeks together with our
subject matter experts you've been in
studio you've been recording all the 40
plus sessions that we have in this
release tell us a little bit what's new
in this release yes thank you l so we
have uh done something a little bit
different this time we've been working
hard in studio as always producing 40
videos and sessions for you guys but we
listened to the community and found out
that you would like a little bit more
shorter bite-sized videos as as well as
the long detailed ones so we have
accommodated this in this release so we
will both have the short bsize one which
will both go with detail what is new
within specifically this new release but
also guide you to previous launch events
videos on YouTube so you can get the
whole picture and all the information
that you need and we will also have a
little bit of the longer videos with
more details for what is completely new
in this release and all of these will be
available this time on our YouTube front
page uh after this opening session so go
and check them out Maya that's
amazing we hope you will enjoy the new
format as well um but let's take a sneak
peek into the new lease let's invite
Yanik and Dimitri to get us
started thank you L and Maya for having
us today so I'm Yanik Bower and I'm
Dimitri chadv and what we're going to do
uh now is take you through a lot of the
improvements we've done in this release
I will start by talking to what we done
in AI powered business and I will of
course cover everything there is to know
about the world class service yes but
let me start and then I'll invite you
back a little bit later diit sure the
floor is yours thank you very much so as
you can see here there are a lot of
investments in this release both
enhancements but also Innovations what
we've done now is and what we will do is
Tak you through most of them there will
still be a few of them because we can't
fit everything in of all these great cap
capabilities in uh the next uh period
here so first of all co-pilot shouldn't
be a surprise that we've done a lot of
investments in co-pilot in this release
and first of all uh I think it's worth
to mention that you can now start using
co-pilot without having to set up
anything that basically means it's
default on there is of course one place
where you can go the co-pilot and AI
capabilities page and that's where you
can administer what should be on and
what should be on if you're an admin in
the company here so that you are in
control of this now what do we do to
chat because chat is of course one of
the First Investments here we have in in
the product and what we looked at is
helping users being better at doing data
inquiries so if a user wres for example
in this case you know show me the top
customers what co-pilot will do it will
actually link to the analysis View and
open a copilot generated analysis tab
with that in information so the chat
knows exactly you know awareness of what
goes on in in business Central helps the
user navigate it's also aware of the
current pages on so whether it's a
customer page or customer list in this
case or an item list you could then ask
let's say it's a list saying show me all
the blue items on this page that uh is
also possible now in the in the chat
pane it's become more knowledgeable and
how that how come that that's because we
now make sure that reads and knows about
the release PL so of course all the
features we have in this release users
can then ask questions about it but also
reading through all the learn content
not only what is on docs but also our
training materials that's now in the um
in in copilot in this release and of
course what we know from users is they
need uh some prompt examples to get
started so we added a lot more on these
small uh view prompts um icons that we
have throughout the product so go
explore that go explore all that with
your customers and
Prospects when we talk about analysis
assist with co-pilot what we've also
done here is make it possible to review
you know what you ask copilot to build
but also adjust and then jump between in
this case the different analysis tabs
generated and that helps you as a user
really saying No this is what I want and
then say keep it at that point and you
can add hidden fields that you don't
necessarily see on the page that's also
possible to add
uh through the co-pilot chat here it's
one of the most used features so um if
you if if you haven't already got
customers to adopt this I think uh you
you should go and if you are a customer
go and explore
this and now to supported languages one
of the of course the big request is when
is it coming in my language adding 20
languages with this release it's now
available in all these languages so go
again explore in your own language chat
with uh with co-pilot build the analysis
views within your own language that is
also one of the key investments in this
release co-pilot for finance is a
separate app from Microsoft it's a team
that really looks into what does a
finance team really need what kind of
scenarios will really help them when we
take them and apply co-pilot to that and
that's where co-pilot for finance for
example helps the helps the collection
team uh to respond to emails uh but also
summarize emails if somebody asked about
what they owe to the company you can
then also um uh handle disputes and
dispute status synchronize that back to
business Central and also uh change for
example if there's a new promise to pay
date so a tight integration with
business Central in this release there
is much more to come from that team uh
they are looking into also building a
teams experience uh and adding more
capabilities so go explore that both as
the customers and partners out there um
then we have looked throughout business
Central uh in terms of where could we
really um help users be more productive
uh when you create a new item you often
want what uh about our substitutions so
in this case you would go to the the
substitution screen here the user would
select substitutions and then just click
on generate with co-pilot co-pilot will
then go through business Central and
then suggest in this case a lot of other
chip years just think about the amount
of times saved uh by using copile in
this scenario by the way this is also
available for Dimensions unit of measure
and
variance then we also um have now uh the
possibility with copile to suggest
number series I am actually really happy
about this one because this is a
contribution from one of our MVPs so if
you watch out there thank you um so we
have the possibility for for for anybody
to actually contribute through GitHub
and this was a contribution that
utilizes co-pilot to help generate these
number series and if you start for
example on a blank screen here a blank
number series there's quite a lot to
fill out for all documents and so on but
co-pilot will help a user to
automatically set those up of course you
can in the prompt specify uh certain
names for it certain you know should it
started this number or not uh you could
prepare also number is when you started
next year so a lot of great uh time
saving in setting up this
now and then in terms of we talk often
about feature Improvement this is not a
feat this is a whole capability area
subscription billing it's quite
interesting I mean both you customers
out there but also Partners listening in
and you often either sell something on
subscription at least Partners they sell
Microsoft software on subscription plans
but until now we didn't have really rich
capability for that in the product but
that's now available where you can set
up service contracts you can set up the
billing uh periods and of course it will
also take care of Revenue recognition
which is important when somebody for
example has a subscription that goes
into the next fiscal year all that is
taken care of so go explore that if you
are having um a need for subscription
billing in your company or as a partner
to send out bills and when we talk about
improvements overall for the last couple
of releases or actually quite many
releases we've had a focus on making
sure we deliver Rich analytic and
reports we just saw analysis view really
helping users with ad hoc but of course
uh you as customers and partners out
there also presenting business Central
often want to show something that is
expected and it is expected that when
you open business Central that you can
see the generic like you know income
what's my turnover what's my profit and
so on and all that is now 70 plus
powerbi reports with this release so it
goes with all the areas here on the
slide but also we exploring of course
adding it to areas like manufacturing uh
going forward and other areas in
business Central so a much much greater
experience when you walk up to business
centr for the first time or if your
existing user want to see more uh
reporting capabilities talking about
reporting Financial reboring in business
Central is something that a lot of users
are using because often um there is a
specific need to set it up specifically
to the company we Supply and have
supplied 12 more financial reports in
this uh release but also made sure
there's many more row and column
definitions that the customer the user
can pick down from the shelf and you can
build your own uh Financial reports that
you need so again a lot more out of box
in this area for this
release sustainability uh and if we look
now I'm here in the EU I know there's
also a lot of things being mandated in
Australia around the world and many
regions uh Belgium so on um which is
also in the EU by the way but that's a
so uh what I'm going to say here is
sustainability tracking is something we
hear from all our uh customers having a
demand for saying you know you are
asking for this because you need in many
cases depending on the size of the
company to actually submit uh these
numbers to the government and therefore
we built a rich sustainability tracking
module inside business Central with row
center with scorecards with goals uh
recording greenhouse gases both carbon
credits and so on so go explore that if
that's one of the areas you need to
deliver
on project and service that's a area
that uh we have invested in uh
throughout uh the last release basically
listening to all the needs from you
you're pointing to other areas in the
product where we needed to learn from
those and actually build it in to
projects and service management whether
it was extended text archiving and so on
it is all there now so also go watch
that session if you're interested in
that Shopify Shopify is such a high
demand out there and that also means we
get a lot of feedback on you know
improvements we can do do to it or if
Shopify adds new features we will
improve the integration we see partners
coming back and saying actually Jo that
the Sal Cycles on this is some of the
shortest they ever explored because
there's 2.5 million Shopify shops active
today out in the market and a lot of
those have a need for a greater
integration that is fast to set up and
that's what we can do with business
Central and it's getting better and
better so go explore if you're looking
into the in e-commerce opportunity
Frontline workers there's two billion of
those out there and the way to address
those is through the integration to
Microsoft Dynamics 365 field service we
started in the last release with
something around projects now it's
integrated with service order giving you
a really rich full complete you know
both back office but also front office
uh capabilities to businesses doing
service um in the market so again if you
either a customer you know want to do
even more in that area go explore that
or as a partner go explore that
opportunity Power Platform as you all
know we've invested over many releases
in this first powerbi one thing is
shipping all these rich powerbi reports
we actually in this release making it
much easier to work with them embedded
inside business Central so you don't in
many cases need to leave business uh
Central at all but can just use all
these rich reports directly inside the
product and of course we continue to
uptake and improve the whole experience
with using power automate inside
business Central for building uh flows
and workflows uh for any business
process there and the last one I want
say that job Q notification via power
automate flows it's actually something I
know that's not in any slides but we
have actually made it possible now to
get the job queue notification when
something is maybe you know there's a
challenge there it will show on the role
senders in this release but also it's
possible to build a um a flow that sends
a notification to the right users in the
company this is something many of course
in non-english speaking ask for the
access keys that we added many people
users out there use the keyboard to be
productive here we have French now
access keys are available in all the
languages on this slide in this release
we are also improving uh search it's in
preview uh right now in this month it
will come out uh in next month but
that's basically the possibility to um
select between the mother or Legacy
search the difference here is the
mothern would look full text search in
those columns that we are Partners have
marked for that whereas Legacy search
will search throughout everything inside
a business Central and using Legacy
search is of course a little more slow
where the modern search is fast it has
the fulltech search not just the whole
string there character matching so this
is actually delivering what the user
would expect when searching for
something and of course also the
possibility to use the ant operator in
there a just much faster and better
experience in the product resize column
you would think haven't we be able to do
that in business Central sometime yes we
were but that required you go into
personalization and whatever device you
jumped on it would remember that that's
great but sometimes you just want to
resize in the moment and resize on the
screen you're on you can do that now
without going into personalization mode
another great feature we get a lot of
feedback on word reporting uh document
reports in business Central they're rich
uh uh when you use a word but of course
we've also got the feedback that uh some
conditional um formatting is needed not
show this field when this is not that's
now possible there's also the
possibility to change between word
layouts so another investment we are
doing and delivering on now to make it
much more richer word laid out
experience with business
Central I mentioned before that there
was a contribution uh from GitHub to the
product there's are actually
156 Community uh contribut tions in this
release so thank you again to everybody
out there that has contributed through
GitHub where we then have the product
manager review Engineers review working
with you to make the product just much
better that's such a great thing that we
as a community can build a better
product it's in many areas it's in
connectors it's in the horizontal
capabilities it's in the business
features it's also sensibility events
and so on Buck fixes paper cuts that we
just need to clean out and and of course
Ai and copil pilot features so with that
I'm actually going to have Dimitri back
on stage and tell us about all the other
things we've done in this release as
well thank you Demitri thank you very
much Yanik amazing set of capabilities
I'm pretty sure there's many of you
waiting for this already out there and
the release is available so why are you
waiting you should go ahead and try many
of these features as well of course I'm
going to talk uh a lot about the
worldclass service and this release is
not an exception uh we did build a lot
of capabilities in the service to make
it much more secure reliable performance
and always available to the customers so
the lon's share of the Investments is
lying there by us analyzing Telemetry
and making sure that the service is
always available always secure and
always running but for some of you
administrators out there administrating
customer environments we did want to
address some of the biggest asks in the
industry for example with this
capability the one which is called
flexible update management I'm pretty
sure many of you like the sound of that
whatever we make flexible is great for
the customers now I wanted to mention
that this capability is coming out in
preview and what is it this is ability
for the administrators to postpone the
updates to for a longer period of time
so basically the window of scheduling
the update is becoming a little bit
longer and how much longer you might ask
is actually quite a bit longer for those
of you who really really need this
capability so you can see that it goes
from 60 days to 5 months this is how
long you can uh keep working on the on
on the on the solution keep finding the
right moment in time to apply the update
I wanted to make it crystal clear to all
of you watching the uh the video and uh
well the live translation actually in
this case we still encourage many of you
to and all of you to keep latest to make
sure that your Solutions are easily
updatable to the next version we are
making a lot of efforts to keep them
compatible and easy to update however we
also understand that each business is
different and there are terms and
conditions where you do want to find
that perfect time to update your
environment and now you got a lot more
flexibility in this process uh to
schedule to find the right uh moment of
time to do the update so I'm hoping that
that many of you are fairly happy uh
with this this new change but I'm also
hoping that many of you will never use
it and will go along with our update
Cadence and stay current on the very
latest versions of business
Central another capability which I
wanted to bring up here is related to
assigning Partners to specific
environments we see many customers out
there using multiple environments in
business Central which is a very very
convenient feature and sometimes
especially when this collaboration goes
across country let's say there is an
environment in Germany and there is an
environment in France these customers
sometimes work with different partners
and of course the requirement is how can
we limit access to uh for this
particular partner to this particular
environment and that is now available in
the tenant admin center with a click of
a button essentially you can assign the
partner of record the delegated admin to
a specific environment and they will
only have access to that specific
environment which is great news in terms
of uh protecting your environments and
keeping the control uh Access Control to
uh to what is really really needed also
for those of you uh who would like to
get much more control and much more
insight into what admins are doing in
business Central environments we now
introducing a capability to log all of
the administrative uh uh requests and
all of the administrative actions
performed in the admin Center and in the
application into Microsoft 365 priew log
this is the all up Microsoft solution
for auditing uh admin operations and now
business Central is part of that happy
family so much easier to audit uh
different admin operations across the
stock across the Microsoft
portfolio now moving into the amazing
world of devops I'm pretty sure many of
you are working with uh UPS out there so
you work with pertinent extensions you
work with isv Solutions and the solution
from Microsoft which helps you and your
partners and your isvs to manage this
solution is Al go for GitHub and Al go
for GitHub just become became better
with this release it keeps being
refreshed with every iteration and this
release is not exception for instance we
applied a lot of security hardening to
the devop solution so now many of you
using the algo for GitHub in get and
inherit these security improvements to
run your pipeline security securely and
and operate in this environment much
more protected and secure way we also
added a fantastic capability for you to
easily test your Solutions uh for
compatibility with all of the isv apps
which you depend on so now out of the
box if your isvs decided to plug in into
this system and share there symbols with
you you can any day any time of the day
test whether your solution is compatible
with the current and future version of
your isv uh app which is an amazing
capability so you can always be in
control and always stay ahead of the
changes applied by whether it's
Microsoft or whether it's your isv
solution which is a great Improvement as
well one other thing which I wanted to
cover here is performance I'm pretty
sure that many of you would like to
build performance solutions we
definitely strongly encourage you to do
so and AO for GitHub will help you in
this journey what is possible with Al go
for GitHub is to set up the environment
where you can create the Baseline for
all of your performance tests so you
basically run a set of tests to measure
the current performance of your solution
of your application and then use it as a
baseline for all of the future checks
and changes in your application whether
it's pertinent extension or isv so you
can see exactly how much impact on
performance your changes introduced in
the system so here for example on the
screen you see some of the warnings some
of the messages the things get better
performance- wise or worth and you can
easily track that with Alo for GitHub
and make decisions whether to update the
baseline or whether to go ahead and
improve the
code definitely something to check out
in the space of Al and Al language our
application language and the development
environment which is Visual Studio code
there's just so many changes that I I I
had hard time fitting them on the same
slide so I listed some of them some of
the Fantastic capabilities uh such as
interface improvements I'm pretty sure
many of you Building extensible
Solutions use interfaces a lot we now
have a support for save as Json for on
the query object which I'm pretty sure
many of you will will use uh some of the
capabilities to modify and update
settings for page extensions allowing
inserts modifies deletes so all of these
capabilities will just make your
development Li life easier and there's
many more in the box so please watch
this session and uh discover what's uh
what's available for for all of you Al
developers out
there now one interesting capability
which is kind of development but it's
intended for the consultant out there
and the power users out there uh this is
not the new investment this is something
we started in the previous release as
well and we wanted to make it much
easier for you to navigate from the
beautiful fantastic AI uh sorry AI as
well and UI of business Central user
experience in business Central to the
code behind this page so that should be
easy sometimes the code is the best
instructions and the best documentation
for what is in the business Central not
always but sometimes also you may want
to use it for troubleshooting if a very
specific scenario is acting in a strange
way you can now easily with a click of a
button uh set up the debugger and then
go through this flow and then figure out
what the problem is what we updated in
this release is ability for this flow
open and visual studio code to interact
with your GitHub repository so now you
can make sure that whatever you're
looking at whatever code you're looking
at whatever version you look can add is
the latest version and is the right
version which is saved safely and
soundly in your GitHub repository this
adds a lot of reliability to to all of
you inspecting the code Behind these
beautiful business Central Pages again
it's it's very easy to activate so take
a look at it and and give it a
try uh couple of releases ago we we
realized that Microsoft uh is not the
only one who is excited which is excited
about AI all of you Partners jumped in
and wanted to build Solutions using the
co-piloting business Central and for
that we introduce the AI toolkit so AI
toolkit is a tool for you to design for
for partners and for isvs to design AI
infused scenarios in business Central
and it comes with a lot of samples a lot
it comes with a lot of uh code and the
and the Beautiful The Prompt dialogue
with a lot of capabilities built into it
so you can basically basically just
focus on designing the business logic
and everything that is to to do with
talking to Ai and working with prompts
that is facilitated with this
development tool so in this release we
extend in the capabilities of the
developer tool for uh co-pilot and
business Central with several more very
cool capabilities for example uh so now
the co-pilot actions are available on
many more pages so you can go ahead and
Infuse them into into other elements of
business Central the prom dialogue can
now surface the messages and error
messages from your code directly into
the UI of the prom dialogue so that
there's no annoying uh popups and for
the user experience it's surfaced in a
very nice and userfriendly way and the
customers can can read the text and
react accordingly change their prompt or
or do something to to avoid uh having
this uh error um we one particular
interest in capability is emitting
Telemetry for all of the AI usage uh to
to the isvs and partners out there who
can understand what is it is being how
the customers are using the AI in their
Solutions now one absolutely critical
thing to mention here that there's
absolutely no customer data emitted with
this Telemetry so it is a pure metadata
uh pure knowledge about you know which
actions were in enabled and how many
runs were were performed so there's no
customer data available with this
Telemetry however all of those AI
Builders can understand how the
customers interact with the AI features
which is a very amazing opportunity out
there there's there's a full session
dedicated to improvements to function
call in Ai and this is to deep to cover
in this interaction so I'm just going to
speak skip over and I'm sure many of you
interested in that will go and and watch
the
recording now one interesting thing
which I which we bringing into into the
toolkit for co-pilot and business
Central is ability to test now ai is an
interesting technology so it's no longer
if then else code it's something that
evolves with the different prompts it
provides slightly different uh results
and you as a developer you want to get
ahead of it and understand how to test
these capabilities
testing AI is an interesting case and
what you typically want to do you want
to make sure that you have the right
data you have the right test Suite uh
which covers your AI scenario and
provides some outcomes and then you can
test these outcomes whether they are
expected outcomes or not you can use
this tool in combination with Azure AI
Studio to get even more value of testing
your AI features Azure AI studio is
fantastic in testing scenarios such as
harm testing or testing for malicious
intent so you can also make sure that
your code and your prompt are is is are
ready for uh to to dismiss all of this
uh unwanted input Into Your solution so
please take a look at the preview which
we published at aka.ms BC ups and
definitely watch the session to learn
much more about how to run the test tool
kit for
AI now and here's the example of things
that that you would uh need to test in
the past so in the current situation you
have a co-pilot extension and you have a
few procedures for testing but you
needed much more to be able to test AI
you needed your own test Suites and your
own data sets so for that we built the
the testing uh tool for you for all of
you co-pilot
Builders I wanted to just briefly touch
upon the manage di resources we did
announce it in the previous release
which means that instead of for all of
your solutions for all of your icv
Solutions using AI instead of bringing
your own Azure AI subscription you can
run against Microsoft managed AI
resources and uh not having to care
about managing this at a higher scale so
this provides you out with out of the
box ability to just use AI resources
from Microsoft and focus on the business
logic and focus on building the business
business value now we're going to update
you much more in this area but one thing
which we wanted to bring up here is that
we are gradually coming to the place
where we would like to expand this
private preview into the public preview
so there will definitely be a further
announcements on this topic and you will
get to to learn how to get into the
public preview where all of you can can
try uh Building Solutions in that
way now back on to the topic of
performance this is an interesting one
now it has become so increasingly
difficult to find performance
bottlenecks in business Central that we
started going into the scenarios like
the one that you see on your screen for
example you may have have found yourself
in the situations where uh a certain
place in the application is starting to
be uh to behave slowly but only in
certain circumstances so not all the
time but sometimes and I'm sure all of
you already learned that uh if you want
to kind of take a look at performance
and what is taking time we have this
beautiful tool called in client
performance profiler which you can uh
start from from the client and measure
your scenario and then see exactly where
the time is spent uh in which extension
in which code the time is spent in this
particular scenario but what we add in
with this release is ability to schedule
these profiles to run in the background
so what you can set up as an as as a
user wishing to understand what is
causing kind of the performance uh
challenges in one or the other part of
the of the application you can set up to
run in the background and then in the
end of the hour the end of the day the
end of the week you can expect these
scheduled profiles find exactly the ones
which caught the moment in time where
the the code was not acting as it should
have and go troubleshoot that profile so
much more much more convenient for all
of you to troubleshoot performance cases
and it is easily available from help and
support page so click of a button and
you can schedule the profile to run uh
in your
environment now talking about
performance improvements I wanted to
mention three areas here uh Yanik
already mentioned uh the new modern
fantastic search it is indeed much
faster we did hear so many uh asks from
you in the past
the people working with large amount of
data I know that many of you are working
with hundreds of thousands of items in
your inventory and search was not
performing uh in those circumstances so
this new and improved modern search is
working much faster as a data search
solution as a solution to search for
items on the list page in drill downs
and lookups so the search has become
much faster with this uh with this
version of the business Central
we also to optimize the job queue flow
uh now in the past it was not certain
that the first job queue which was
scheduled is going to be the one that
will run first and we made it so that in
this release it is the case so the first
job that comes in that is the job that
is going to be uh processed the moment
that the service has resources to
process it and that also enabled the
opportunity to inject the priority into
job Q category so for instance some jobs
may have higher priority compared to
others so now you can use job cues
categories to assign this priority to
your jobs and they will get executed
sooner than the jobs in other categories
which is amazing Improvement for all of
you working with job cues and finally we
refactored the process of posting into
warehouse Ledger entry which is an
amazing story I do encourage you to go
and watch this video it's a whole new
pattern which was invented for that
purpose which introduces which kind of
decreases locking in this scenario by a
large large extent so the posting into
warehouse Ledger entries is now much
more concurrent and therefore you can
get much more throughput in this
scenario so we're not stopping in this
space we'll continue promoting this
pattern and use this pattern in other
scenarios in the application as
well now now you may remember one of the
tools uh which we announced in the
previous release called page scripting
great tool fantastic tool for all of you
wishing to create your own tests without
having to write code so what you can do
with this tool you can simply go to the
user interface of business Central
capture the the user flow using the
actions and record it and then replay
again and again and again to see whether
the the scenario still works after some
changes so we did apply some changes
some user experience changes to this
tool but one of the bigger improvements
here is that we also made it available
uh for all of you administrators and
devops people to run it in pipelines so
now these tests which you record in the
user experience can also run in
pipelines and you can run them
recurrently you can schedule recurrent
run uh of these tests uh just like you
schedule the tests of any other type of
test automation so definitely something
to inspect as well and and look forward
to
so this was a great overview from Yanik
and hopefully some of the great features
from me as well of 2024 release Wave 2
and I just wanted to say please join the
q&as with our amazing team of product
managers and developers working on this
product hands on uh with the like with
the firsthand knowledge of all of these
processes come to these sessions about
co-pilot Power Platform user experiences
application localizations local features
and Reporting as well as development
Administration service and platform and
and talk to the experts behind the
behind all of these features that we've
just presented now I know that many of
you are not necessarily in the Central
European Time Zone so for don't get
confused uh don't get discouraged if you
go to aka.ms BC launch event and you
sign up for a Q&A session then it will
conveniently create a calendar
appointment for you in your time zone
and then you're absolutely certain you
will meet the experts in this in this
time
window yes and of course if you uh are
not joining the Q&A sessions but just
want to watch the recordings they are
available now on YouTube so again you
know the shortcut akms slbc YouTube and
this is a list of all of the sis and
remember remember the change as uh L and
Meer said in the beginning is we really
you know reduced the the length of these
to focus on the core of what are really
the Improvement there so we hope that uh
this time around if you're interested in
any of these that you get to complete
all of them or at least those within the
area that you are interested in so with
that um thank you very much for for this
um yeah this release so to say and thank
you to the teams also I know they
upstairs watching in I also know that a
lot of both partners and customers out
there have a lot of you know events and
so on so thank you for spending the time
with us and watching this uh new release
thank you so much thank you
[Music]